I've been provided with some incomplete
verses from various greeting cards which
I'd like you to try to finish off, okay?
Marcus, let's start with you. This is an
apology card. It goes like this.
I know I hurt you, crossed the line. I
wish that I could rewind time.
It started badly with no plan. I'm sorry
that I bombed Iran.
>> [applause]
>> You now, Richard. It's a Christmas card.
Santa's been, you can be sure. He's left
a trail across the floor.
>> On the carpet we just bought. Pity he
was taken short.
>> Tony, how about this? This is uh it's
it's sorry for your loss. I cannot mend
your broken heart or take away the
aching parts, but I can walk this road
with you.
>> And you can show me where you ran her
over.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Rachel, how about this one? It's uh on
giving birth.
A tiny hand, a little yawn, a brand new
son, a brand new dawn.
>> I hear you tore from hole to hole. So,
here's two paracetamol.
>> [applause]
>> Marcus, sympathy card for a pet snake.
Though others never felt the same, you
loved your snake and that's no shame.
I understand just how you felt, but
goodness, what a lovely belt.
And uh finally, Tony. This is uh sorry
you lost your job card, yeah.
Your job is gone, the paycheck, too,
which puts an awful strain on you, but
>> at least you've got the house in
Sandringham.
>> [applause]